#### Contact

jezarae.larocque.2@my.und.e

www.linkedin.com/in/jezarae-larocque-60150787 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Word

**PowerPoint** 

**CPR Certified** 

### Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

Emergency Medical Technician (EMT)

TNCC

# Jezarae LaRocque

BSN, RN, CCRN

Phoenix, Arizona

## Summary

Experienced Critical Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, First Aid, and Critical Thinking. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from The University of North Dakota.

## Experience

Phoenix Indian Medical Center Registered Nurse February 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months) Phoenix, Arizona

LiquidAgents Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
March 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Mayo Clinic
Critical Care Registered Nurse
March 2016 - Present (4 years 4 months)
Rochester, Minnesota

Altru Health System
Student Nurse Intern
January 2015 - August 2015 (8 months)
Grand Forks, North Dakota Area

Mayo Clinic Student Nurse Extern June 2014 - August 2014 (3 months) Rochester, Minnesota

DAKOTA TRAVEL NURSE Certified Nursing Assistant

August 2013 - April 2014 (9 months)

HOME HEALTH Home Health Aide August 2012 - April 2014 (1 year 9 months) Minto, North Dakota

The MENTOR Network
Direct Support Professional
February 2012 - October 2012 (9 months)
Grand Forks, North Dakota

### Education

The University of North Dakota Bachelor's degree, Registered Nurse BSN · (2010 - 2015)

American College of Norway Study Abroad · (2013 - 2013)

The University of North Dakota BSN